<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DMCommentFile>
  <Comments
         Body_Ground="No visualization for ground. As default the positive X-axle is forward and positive Y-axle is up."
         CoordinateSystem_Pillar.LiftCylinder="Lift cylinder attachment point in Pillar body. "
         CoordinateSystem_Pillar.LiftBoom="Lift boom attachment point in Pillar body. "
         CoordinateSystem_LiftBoom.TiltBoom="Tilt boom attachment point in LiftBoom body. "
         CoordinateSystem_LiftBoom.LiftPiston="Lift cylinder piston attachment point in LiftBoom body. "
         CoordinateSystem_LiftBoom.TiltCylinder="Tilt cylinder attachment point in LiftBoom body. "
         CoordinateSystem_TiltBoom.TiltPiston="Tilt cylinder piston attachment point in TiltBoom body. "
         Dummy_Dummy_LiftCylinder="Adds cylinder visualization graphics for lift force. Attached to first force point when dummy index is 1. Adds also mass and inertia for force components."
         Dummy_Dummy_LiftPiston="Adds piston visualization graphics for force. Attached to second force point when dummy index is 2. Adds also mass and inertia for force components."
         Dummy_Dummy_TiltCylinder="Adds cylinder visualization graphics for lift force. Attached to first force point when dummy index is 1. Adds also mass and inertia for force components."
         Dummy_Dummy_TiltPiston="Adds piston visualization graphics for force. Attached to second force point when dummy index is 2. Adds also mass and inertia for force components."
         Constraint_Ground_Pillar="Revolute joint between Ground and Pillar. Rotational axle Y."
         Constraint_Pillar_LiftBoom="Revolute joint between Pillar and LiftBoom. Rotational axle Z."
         Constraint_LiftBoom_Tiltboom="Revolute joint between LiftBoom and Pillar. Rotational axle Z."
         Graphics_Graphics_Pillar="Reference marker of the graphics is at the same point as the Pillar body."
         Graphics_Graphics_LiftBoom="Reference marker of the graphics is at the same point as the LiftBoom body."
         Graphics_Graphics_TiltBoom="Reference marker of the graphics is at the same point as the TiltBoom body."
         Graphics_Graphics_Cylinder="Scaled to get actual size of the cylinder."
         Graphics_Graphics_Piston="Scaled to get actual size of the piston."
         Spline_Cyl_friction="Friction spline for cylinder stick-slip behavior."
         Spline_Motor_spline="Motor Torque spline. X-axle is rotational speed in [rad/s], Y-axle is torque in [N]"
         B2BF_ForceT_Lift="Only force definition between two bodies. Hydraulic cylinder creates the actual force between bodies."
         B2BF_ForceT_Tilt="Only force definition between two bodies. Hydraulic cylinder creates the actual force between bodies."
         B2BM_ForceR_Pillar="Only force definition between two bodies. Motor creates the actual force between bodies."
         Motor_Rotate_motor="Simple motor model to create rotational movement."
         DV43_DV43_Lift="Symmetric flow in all ports."
         DV43_DV43_Tilt="Symmetric flow in all ports."
         Hose_Hose_LiftCyl_A="1/4 &quot; hose"
         Hose_Hose_LiftCyl_B="1/4 &quot; hose"
         Hose_Hose_TiltCyl_A="1/4 &quot; hose"
         Hose_Hose_TiltCyl_B="1/4 &quot; hose"
         Hose_Hose_Tank="3/8 &quot; hose"
         Hose_Hose_Pump="3/8 &quot; hose"
         Cylinder_LiftCylinder="50/20 cylinder with 450mm stroke. See reference manual for cylinder dimension definitions."
         Cylinder_TiltCylinder="50/20 cylinder with 450mm stroke. See reference manual for cylinder dimension definitions."
         Volume_Vol_Pump="Constant pressure source. Very simple example to create hydraulics. "
         Volume_Vol_LiftCyl_A="Pressure set to 1bar at start."
         Volume_Vol_LiftCyl_B="Pressure set to 1bar at start."
         Volume_Vol_TiltCyl_A="Pressure set to 1bar at start."
         Volume_Vol_TiltCyl_B="Pressure set to 1bar at start."
         Input_Input_Pillar_Rotate="Input for joystick control. Maximum rotational speed of motor is 140 rad/s, input skaled from 0-1 to 0-140. Dead zone 0.1 to prevent movement when joystick is released. Direction changed with negative value."
         Input_Input_Pillar_Brake="Input for joystick control. Releases brake with 20% of input signal."
         Input_Input_Lift="Input for joystick control. Valve maximum input is 10V. Joystick scaled from 0-1 to 0-10 for full valve opening. Direction changed with negative value."
         Input_Input_Tilt="Input for joystick control. Valve maximum input is 10V. Joystick scaled from 0-1 to 0-10 for full valve opening. Direction changed with negative value."
         Camera_Camera_Side="Camera for side view. This camera is active when simulation starts."
         Camera_Camera_Pillar="Camera view from pillar side."
         Light_Light1="Default light in world." />
  <DesignVariables />
</DMCommentFile>
